

CONTACT

- +251 91 326 8210
- ☑ getdera6591@gmail.com
- Addis Ababa Ethiopia
- www.github.com/dires318
- in <u>linkedin.com/in/dires-aman-890a41215</u>

EDUCATION

2016-2021 ADDIS ABABA SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY

- BSc. Electrical and Computer Engineering
- GPA: 3.83 / 4.0

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Typescript, Python, PHP, Java
- Angular, React, Next.js
- Material UI, Ant D., PrimeReact
- Nest.js, Django, Spring-boot
- Git, Jira, Postgresql, Mysql

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Active learner
- Hard working
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

LANGUAGES

- English (Professional)
- Amharic (Native)

DIRES AMAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Experienced full-stack developer with 3+ years of experience developing custom web applications with Django, Next.js, Nest.js, and Angular. I am currently in charge of development at Nisir IT Solutions. Through close client collaboration, team management, and customized solution delivery, I have successfully completed projects in a variety of industries. My ability to solve problems and communicate effectively allows me to regularly complete projects on time even in fast-paced work settings.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nisir IT Solutions

JUL 2023 - PRESENT

Software Developer

- I work as a team lead and full-stack developer
- I am actively involved in projects such as an e-learning platform, and ERP system.
- Tech stack: Django, Next.js, React

eTechSc.

MAR 2022 - JUL 2023

Software Developer

- · I worked as full-stack developer
- I participated in EMR system project.
- · Tech stack: Angular, React, Spring-boot, vert.x

PROJECTS

E-learning Platform

SEP 2022 - PRESENT

- An online learning platform with tutoring services, offering structured courses.
- https://mytutor.com.et

Erp system

MAR 2023 - PRESENT

- A mini ERP system developed form scratch.
- Includes HR, Payroll, Inventory, production, sales and Finance management
- https://ahadu.nisirtech.com

EMR System

MAR 2022 - JUL 2023

 Handles patient registration, scheduling, triage, pharmacy inventory, ,logistic management and payment management for outpatient, inpatient, and emergency services.

CERTIFICATE

IBM/Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner

March 2020

The earner has acquired knowledge of applying Enterprise Design Thinking and its value

University of Michigan/Building Web Applications in Django April 2024

Coursera certifies their successful completion of Building Web Applications in Django provided by University of Michigan.